A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12 FA284
Rockefeller Archive Center
- State Files, 1921-1962; 2
  - Oklahoma - Statistical Service - Correspondence and Reports, 1944 November 20-1948 September 16 (Box 29, Folder 435-436)
  - Oklahoma - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1944 (Box 29, Folder 437)
  - Tennessee - Budgets and Budget Correspondence, 1929 November 14-1951 June 25 (Box 30, Folder 438-449)
  - Tennessee - Clerical Training - Correspondence and Reports, 1945 July 9-1951 July 26 (Box 31, Folder 450-451)
  - Tennessee - Dental Hygiene Program - Reports, March 5, 1937-June 3, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 452)
  - Tennessee - Field Trip Reports, 1929 December 8-1946 September 5 (Box 31, Folder 453-457)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1930-1932 (Box 31, Folder 458-460)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Quarterly Reports, 1933-1938 (Box 32, Folder 461-463)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Semi-annual Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 32, Folder 464-470)
  - Tennessee - Field Unit Six Year Report, July 1, 1930-June 30, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 471)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, 1931 March 16-1942 September 28 (Box 32, Folder 472-474)
  - Tennessee - Financial Correspondence, 1943 February 22-1951 April 6 (Box 33, Folder 475-479)
  - Tennessee - General Correspondence, Memoranda and Reports, 1928 April 4-1951 September 27 (Box 33, Folder 480-489)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Correspondence, 1930 March 1-1957 September 18 (Box 34, Folder 490-493)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Health Center Correspondence, December 16, 1936-May 3, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 494)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1946 (Box 34, Folder 495)
  - Tennessee - Gibson County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939-1940; 1943 and 1945 (Box 34, Folder 496-503)
  - Tennessee - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1946 (Box 34, Folder 504)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Correspondence, February 21, 1930-December 29, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 505)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Correspondence, 1935 January 11-1956 October 4 (Box 35, Folder 506-508)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Health Center Correspondence, December 18, 1935-November 3, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 509)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1950 (Box 35, Folder 510)
  - Tennessee - Sullivan County - Yearly Report, 1929-1935; 1937; 1939; 1941-1942; 1945 (Box 35, Folder 511-518)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Correspondence and Reports, February 15, 1937-December 30, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 519)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Correspondence and Reports, 1937 February 9-1948 November 23 (Box 36, Folder 520-525)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Evaluation Schedules, 1947 and 1948 (Box 36, Folder 526)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, 1944 January 18-1947 December 19 (Box 36, Folder 527-531)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Health Center Correspondence and Reports, January 23, 1948-October 17, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 532)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Statistical Summaries, 1921-1949 (Box 37, Folder 533)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Tuberculosis Program Correspondence and Memoranda, 1949 February 11-1953 August 7 (Box 37, Folder 534-535)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Tuberculosis Program Reports, 1939 July 1-1948 June 30 (Box 37, Folder 536-538)
  - Tennessee - Sumner County - Yearly Report, 1938-1946 (Box 37, Folder 539-543)
  - Tennessee - University of Tennessee - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, 1930 May 15-1938 June 12 (Box 37, Folder 544-546)
  - Tennessee - Vanderbilt University - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, 1929 December 2-1949 February 26 (Box 38, Folder 547-554)
  - Tennessee - Whooping Cough Program - Correspondence and Reports, December 11, 1942-December 8, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 555)
  - Virginia - Richmond Department of Public Health - Medical Care for Indigents - Financial Statements, July 1, 1949-June 30, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 556)
  - Washington - Field Trip Reports, February 2, 1944-May 15, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 557)
  - Washington - General Correspondence and Memoranda, December 2, 1943-October 9, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 558)
- Public Health Fellowships, 1936-1963; 3
  - Alabama - Postgraduate Medical (A-E), undated (Box 39, Folder 559)
  - Alabama - Postgraduate Medical (G-M), undated (Box 39, Folder 560)
  - Alabama - Postgraduate Medical (N-S), undated (Box 39, Folder 561)
  - Alabama - Postgraduate Medical (T-Z), undated (Box 39, Folder 562)
  - California - California Mental Health Institute (July 1-19, 1948) - Correspondence, June 25, 1948-September 21, 1948 (Box 39, Folder 563)
  - Fellowship Recipient Rosters - Alabama to Miscellaneous Fellowships, undated (Box 39, Folder 564)
  - Fellowship Recipient Rosters - Mississippi to Oklahoma, undated (Box 39, Folder 565)
  - Fellowship Recipient Rosters - Tennessee to Vermont, undated (Box 39, Folder 566)
  - Florida - Postgraduate Medical (C and H), undated (Box 39, Folder 567)
  - Kentucky - Laboratory Technicians (B-Y), undated (Box 39, Folder 568)
  - Kentucky - Postgraduate Medical (B-S), undated (Box 39, Folder 569)
  - Kentucky - Public Health Nursing (S), undated (Box 39, Folder 570)
  - Maine - Postgraduate Medical (A-D), undated (Box 39, Folder 571)
  - Maine - Postgraduate Medical (E-M), undated (Box 39, Folder 572)
  - Maine - Postgraduate Medical (N-T), undated (Box 39, Folder 573)
  - Maine - Undergraduate (M-W), undated (Box 39, Folder 574)
  - Massachusetts - Laboratory Technicians (B-G), undated (Box 40, Folder 575)
  - Massachusetts - Laboratory Technicians (H-J), undated (Box 40, Folder 576)
  - Massachusetts - Laboratory Technicians (M-R), undated (Box 40, Folder 577)
  - Massachusetts - Laboratory Technicians (S-W), undated (Box 40, Folder 578)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (A-C), undated (Box 40, Folder 579)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (D-H), undated (Box 40, Folder 580)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (K-M), undated (Box 40, Folder 581)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (N-R), undated (Box 40, Folder 582)
  - Massachusetts - Postgraduate Medical (S-W), undated (Box 40, Folder 583)
  - Massachusetts - Public Health Nursing (B-E), undated (Box 40, Folder 584)
  - Massachusetts - Public Health Nursing (F-L), undated (Box 40, Folder 585)
  - Massachusetts - Public Health Nursing (M-W), undated (Box 40, Folder 586)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (A-B), undated (Box 41, Folder 587)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (C-F), undated (Box 41, Folder 588)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (G-K), undated (Box 41, Folder 589)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (L-R), undated (Box 41, Folder 590)
  - Massachusetts - Undergraduate (S-Y), undated (Box 41, Folder 591)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Bacteriologists (F-S), undated (Box 41, Folder 592)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Health Officers (B-F), undated (Box 41, Folder 593)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Health Officers (H-P), undated (Box 41, Folder 594)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Health Officers (R-Z), undated (Box 41, Folder 595)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Public Health Nurses (B-P), undated (Box 41, Folder 596)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships - All States - Sanitarians (A-F), undated (Box 41, Folder 597)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships All States - Sanitarians (H-W), undated (Box 41, Folder 598)
  - Miscellaneous Fellowships All States - Survey of Undergraduate Fellowships, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 599)
  - Mississippi - Diagnosis of Cancer - Correspondence, June 30, 1947-October 16, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 600)
  - Mississippi - Laboratory Technicians (A-F), undated (Box 42, Folder 601)
  - Mississippi - Laboratory Technicians (H-P), undated (Box 42, Folder 602)
  - Mississippi - Laboratory Technicians (R-W), undated (Box 42, Folder 603)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (A-Be), undated (Box 42, Folder 604)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Bi-By), undated (Box 42, Folder 605)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (C), undated (Box 42, Folder 606)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (D-E), undated (Box 42, Folder 607)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (F), undated (Box 42, Folder 608)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (G), undated (Box 42, Folder 609)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Ha-He), undated (Box 42, Folder 610)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Hi-J), undated (Box 43, Folder 611)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (K-L), undated (Box 43, Folder 612)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (M), undated (Box 43, Folder 613)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (N-P), undated (Box 43, Folder 614)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (R), undated (Box 43, Folder 615)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Sa-Se), undated (Box 43, Folder 616)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Sh-St), undated (Box 43, Folder 617)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (T-V), undated (Box 43, Folder 618)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Wa-Will), undated (Box 43, Folder 619)
  - Mississippi - Postgraduate Medical (Wils-Z), undated (Box 43, Folder 620)
  - Mississippi - Public Health Nursing (B-D), undated (Box 43, Folder 621)
  - Mississippi - Public Health Nursing (F-L), undated (Box 44, Folder 622)
  - Mississippi - Public Health Nursing (M-P), undated (Box 44, Folder 623)
  - Mississippi - Public Health Nursing (R-W), undated (Box 44, Folder 624)
  - Mississippi - Undergraduate (B), undated (Box 44, Folder 625)
  - Mississippi - Undergraduate (C-D), undated (Box 44, Folder 626)
  - Mississippi - Undergraduate (E-F), undated (Box 44, Folder 627)
  - Mississippi - Undergraduate (G-J), undated (Box 44, Folder 628)
  - Mississippi - Undergraduate (L-Me), undated (Box 44, Folder 629)
  - Mississippi - Undergraduate (Mi-O), undated (Box 44, Folder 630)
  - Mississippi - Undergraduate (P-R), undated (Box 44, Folder 631)
  - Mississippi - Undergraduate (S-W), undated (Box 44, Folder 632)
  - New Hampshire - Postgraduate (B-C), undated (Box 45, Folder 633)
  - New Hampshire - Postgraduate (D-H), undated (Box 45, Folder 634)
  - New Hampshire - Postgraduate (J-L), undated (Box 45, Folder 635)
  - New Hampshire - Postgraduate (M-O), undated (Box 45, Folder 636)
  - New Hampshire - Postgraduate (P-R), undated (Box 45, Folder 637)
  - New Hampshire - Postgraduate (S-W), undated (Box 45, Folder 638)
  - New Hampshire - Undergraduate (C-W), undated (Box 45, Folder 639)
  - Oklahoma - Laboratory Technicians (A-R), undated (Box 45, Folder 640)
  - Oklahoma - Postgraduate Medical (A-C), undated (Box 45, Folder 641)
  - Oklahoma - Postgraduate Medical (D-G), undated (Box 45, Folder 642)
  - Oklahoma - Postgraduate Medical (H-K), undated (Box 45, Folder 643)
  - Oklahoma - Postgraduate Medical (L-M), undated (Box 45, Folder 644)
  - Oklahoma - Postgraduate Medical (N-P), undated (Box 46, Folder 645)
  - Oklahoma - Postgraduate Medical (R), undated (Box 46, Folder 646)
  - Oklahoma - Postgraduate Medical (S), undated (Box 46, Folder 647)
  - Oklahoma - Postgraduate Medical (T-V), undated (Box 46, Folder 648)
  - Oklahoma - Postgraduate Medical (W-Y), undated (Box 46, Folder 649)
  - Oklahoma - Public Health Nursing (B-Y), undated (Box 46, Folder 650)
  - Statistician Fellowships - All States (D-L), undated (Box 46, Folder 651)
  - Statistician Fellowships - All States (P-W), undated (Box 46, Folder 652)
  - Tennessee - Dentists (H and R), undated (Box 46, Folder 653)
  - Tennessee - Health Education (J-W), undated (Box 46, Folder 654)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (A-Ba), undated (Box 46, Folder 655)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Be-Bl), undated (Box 46, Folder 656)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Bo), undated (Box 46, Folder 657)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Br-Bu), undated (Box 46, Folder 658)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Ca-Ch), undated (Box 47, Folder 659)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Cl), undated (Box 47, Folder 660)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Co-Cr), undated (Box 47, Folder 661)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (D-E), undated (Box 47, Folder 662)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (F-He), undated (Box 47, Folder 663)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Hi-Ho), undated (Box 47, Folder 664)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Hu-I), undated (Box 47, Folder 665)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (J), undated (Box 47, Folder 666)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (K), undated (Box 47, Folder 667)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (L), undated (Box 47, Folder 668)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Ma-Me), undated (Box 47, Folder 669)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Mo-O), undated (Box 48, Folder 670)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (P), undated (Box 48, Folder 671)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (R), undated (Box 48, Folder 672)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (S), undated (Box 48, Folder 673)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (T-Wh), undated (Box 48, Folder 674)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Wi), undated (Box 48, Folder 675)
  - Tennessee - Postgraduate Medical (Wo-Y), undated (Box 48, Folder 676)
  - Tennessee - Public Health Nursing (A-Bri), undated (Box 48, Folder 677)
  - Tennessee - Public Health Nursing (Bro-Bu), undated (Box 48, Folder 678)
  - Tennessee - Public Health Nursing (C-E), undated (Box 48, Folder 679)
  - Tennessee - Public Health Nursing (F-H), undated (Box 48, Folder 680)
  - Tennessee - Public Health Nursing (J-L), undated (Box 49, Folder 681)
  - Tennessee - Public Health Nursing (M-P), undated (Box 49, Folder 682)
  - Tennessee - Public Health Nursing (R-W), undated (Box 49, Folder 683)
  - Tennessee - Undergraduate (A-Be), undated (Box 49, Folder 684)
  - Tennessee - Undergraduate (Bo-Bu), undated (Box 49, Folder 685)
  - Tennessee - Undergraduate (C-D), undated (Box 49, Folder 686)
  - Tennessee - Undergraduate (E-G), undated (Box 49, Folder 687)
  - Tennessee - Undergraduate (H-J), undated (Box 49, Folder 688)
  - Tennessee - Undergraduate (L-M), undated (Box 49, Folder 689)
  - Tennessee - Undergraduate (O-S), undated (Box 49, Folder 690)
  - Tennessee - Undergraduate (T-Z), undated (Box 49, Folder 691)
  - Travel Fellowships (All States) - Report on Commonwealth Fund Travel Fellowship, October 3, 1936 (Box 50, Folder 692)
  - Vermont - Postgraduate (B-E), undated (Box 50, Folder 693)
  - Vermont - Postgraduate (F-H), undated (Box 50, Folder 694)
  - Vermont - Postgraduate (J-M), undated (Box 50, Folder 695)
  - Vermont - Postgraduate (O-R), undated (Box 50, Folder 696)
  - Vermont - Postgraduate (S), undated (Box 50, Folder 697)
  - Vermont - Postgraduate (T-W), undated (Box 50, Folder 698)
  - Vermont - Undergraduate (B-W), undated (Box 50, Folder 699)